

### +91 9952184858

- prathaptamizhan@gmail.com
- 12/33, Yadhava Street Sankaranpalayam, Vellore – 632001 Tamil Nadu

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Computer Application

Indian Institute of Industry Interaction Education and Research

2017 - 2020

## **EXPERTISE**

Analytical skills

Computer skills

Performance Evaluation

Histogram

Communication

## LANGUAGE

English

Tamil

# PRATHAP.B

Quality Analyst

### **ABOUT ME**

I am an energetic, ambitious person who has developed a mature and responsible approach to any task that I undertake. As a graduate with more than four years of experience in management, I am frontline at working with others to achieve a certain objective on time and with excellence. In my previous roles, I always tried to attempt many challenges to improve the performance, operations, and productivity of my team in every segment.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2021 - 2022 Uber, Hyderabad

# Quality Analyst

My responsibilities include call monitoring and providing actionable insights, also analyzed and accumulating information to improve agent performance in the contact center. As the Quality Analyst, audit 70 calls from deferent projects I monitor customer interactions and drafted and executed quality assurance policies and procedures.

2018 - 2020

Uber, Teleperformance, Mohali

### **Customer Care Executive**

Conducted quality assurance surveys with customers and provided feedback to the staff. Possessed excellent product knowledge to enhance customer support, and maintained a pleasant working environment for our team.